<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-10-02T07:27:33+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Loss function Lecture 1</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/LossConcept/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Loss function Lecture 1"/><published>2024-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-10-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/LossConcept</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/LossConcept/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="loss-function">Loss function</h1> <p>Hadi Sadoghi Yazdi</p> <p>A person clusters objects using a loss function that is specific to the conditions and the individual applying it. However, it is more accurate to say that they organize their actions based on the perceived benefits and losses.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossinLife-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossinLife-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossinLife-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossinLife.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Loss in mind. </div> <p>Throughout their lives, whether consciously or unconsciously, humans think about concepts like death, health, poverty, pain, a short life, fear, and so on, which in a way represent the losses they face. Loss is also present in buying and selling, the stock market, marriage, partnerships, and life in general. Different people perceive loss in different ways. Some magnify mistakes, some trim them down, and others correct them.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PerspectiveofLoss-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PerspectiveofLoss-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PerspectiveofLoss-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PerspectiveofLoss.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <h2 id="types-of-loss-functions"><strong>Types of Loss Functions</strong></h2> <p>Loss functions are a key component in machine learning and statistical models, used to quantify the difference between predicted and actual values. They guide optimization algorithms to minimize error and improve model performance. Different types of loss functions are designed to handle various data characteristics and objectives, such as absolute errors, squared errors, or more robust alternatives like <em>Pseudo-Huber</em> and <em>LnCosh</em>, which manage outliers and non-differentiability effectively.</p> <h3 id="absolute-error-loss-function">absolute error loss function</h3> <p>In the absolute error loss function, a sample may fall in different directions relative to the reference index, resulting in positive or negative errors if we think in scalar terms. The loss that affects us generally takes the form of an absolute value. A widely used loss function in many applications is the <em>Absolute Error</em> loss function. Essentially, we place a function between the loss and error, transforming the concept of error into loss. If we introduce some degree of leniency into the loss function, a region of insensitivity to error can be added. Naturally, to achieve this, we lower the absolute value slightly by subtracting an amount of \(\epsilon\). The region of insensitivity is created using the function \(\text{max}(e - \epsilon, 0)\). However, calculating the absolute error index, which is not differentiable and has an insensitive region, presents challenges.</p> \[e = x - \mu\] <p>Where:</p> <ul> <li>\(e\) = error</li> <li>\(x\) = sample</li> <li>\(\mu\) = reference index</li> </ul> <p>To make the absolute error differentiable, <em>LnCosh</em> or <em>Pseudo-Huber</em> is used. To create an insensitivity region, the function \(\text{max}(e^2 - \epsilon, 0)\) is applied. Of course, solving this issue, where the absolute value is non-differentiable and creates an insensitive region, introduces difficulties in calculating \(\mu\), such as making the absolute value differentiable. For this, methods like <em>LnCosh</em> or <em>Pseudo-Huber</em> are employed. This helps when differentiation is needed in computations, allowing us to reach an optimal \(\mu\). Alternatively, magnifying the error function by using the sum of squared errors \(e^2\) can also be applied. By subtracting an amount of \(\epsilon\) and using \(\text{max}(e^2 - \epsilon, 0)\), an insensitive region is created. This illustrates that by adding a degree of leniency or relaxation, the system becomes more robust to error changes.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossTypes_1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossTypes_1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossTypes_1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/LossTypes_1.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <h1 id="robust-absolout-error">Robust Absolout Error</h1> <p>The absolute function becomes smooth and differentiable with <em>lncosh</em>, and in clustering, <em>lncosh</em> can be modified, for instance, by adding the concept of fairness. This prevents outliers (very large errors) from skewing the decision-making system. From a data processing perspective, outliers are significant and can negatively affect the estimation of relevant parameters. The solution to dealing with outliers is to strengthen the function. The loss function, in a combination of <em>lncosh</em> and cross-entropy, is expressed as \(1 - e^{-\alpha \ln(\cosh(e))}\). As seen in Figure 12, excessive increases in large errors do not distort the system.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Robust_lncos-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Robust_lncos-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Robust_lncos-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Robust_lncos.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <h1 id="pinball-loss-function"><strong>Pinball Loss Function</strong></h1> <p>From a socialist perspective, the transition from equality to equity emphasizes the need to address systemic disparities rather than merely treating everyone the same. While equality advocates for uniform treatment and access, equity recognizes that individuals come from diverse backgrounds and circumstances, necessitating tailored support to achieve true fairness. This shift aims to dismantle structural inequalities and ensure that resources and opportunities are distributed based on need, promoting a more just and inclusive society.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Equality_Equity1-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Equality_Equity1-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Equality_Equity1-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Equality_Equity1.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <p>One of the commonly used loss functions that is also non-differentiable is the pinball loss function. This loss function is used when the error distribution is not symmetric. It is employed to transition from the concept of equality to equity. In this function, the errors are weighted in such a way that the positive errors are amplified while the negative errors are reduced.The angle coefficient of the pinball loss can vary, allowing the right and left sides to be adjusted.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PinBall_Loss-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PinBall_Loss-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PinBall_Loss-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/PinBall_Loss.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <p>Certain terms such as under-prediction, over-prediction, and non-normal error distribution may lead to the use of the pinball loss function. For instance, we might consider using the Pinball Loss Function in scenarios where we want to predict stock prices based on data such as news information, social information, and the mental state of people in society. This approach allows us to control the parameter τ externally, resulting in more accurate predictions.</p> <p>Similarly, in determining an index, we may want to bias it in a certain direction based on available information. This information can be gathered either from the data itself or from higher-level insights to control the angle coefficient of the Pinball Loss. Additionally, we might incorporate the concept of insensitivity into the Pinball loss function.</p> <h1 id="concept-of-inequality-equality-justice-equity">Concept of Inequality Equality Justice Equity</h1> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Inequality_Equality_Justice_Equity-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Inequality_Equality_Justice_Equity-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Inequality_Equality_Justice_Equity-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/LossBlog/Inequality_Equality_Justice_Equity.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" data-zoomable="" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <h1 id="inequality"><strong>Inequality</strong></h1> <p><strong>Inequality</strong> inherently exists in the model. For example, when data is represented and summarized by a single parameter, the error of each sample will naturally differ from one another based on its distance from the index. Similarly, when the data is modeled with a single plane, not all samples will lie on that plane, leading to inequality introduced by the model used. If we desire a model that perfectly fits the data, it would require a complex model that is not easily presented and lacks generalizability.</p> <p>Inequality can be viewed as a type of noise in the modeling process, sometimes resembling the effects of system looseness that contributes to stability. This is similar to the looseness used in bridges, which dampens the effects of temperature changes or sudden forces.</p> <h1 id="equality">Equality</h1> <p>Equality means providing opportunities so that everyone is treated equally from the system’s perspective. This does not imply that the system provides equal resources for each individual. Therefore, the loss function acts like a filter that is applied uniformly to all, but some may pass through while others may not. It utilizes a loss function that aggregates all into a cost function with equal weights, similar to:</p> \[L_{\text{equality}} = \sum_{i=1}^{n} (y_i - \hat{y}_i)^2\]]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This lecture guide for better understanding of loss function mechanism]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">the Indoor Positioning System Team</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/IPS_Team/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="the Indoor Positioning System Team"/><published>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/IPS_Team</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/IPS_Team/"><![CDATA[<hr/> <h3 id="introducing-the-indoor-positioning-system-team">Introducing the Indoor Positioning System Team</h3> <p>We are excited to introduce our dedicated team behind the Indoor Positioning System project. This diverse group of professionals combines expertise in various fields, including computer science, engineering, and data analytics, to develop innovative solutions for indoor navigation.</p> <p><strong>Team Members:</strong></p> <ul> <li> <p><strong>[Javad Jaafari]</strong> – Project Lead<br/> With extensive experience in system design and project management, [Member Name] oversees the project’s direction, ensuring we meet our objectives on time.</p> </li> <li> <p><strong>[ Naji]</strong> – Software Engineer<br/> Specializing in algorithm development and software integration, [Member Name] is responsible for creating the algorithms that power our positioning technology.</p> </li> <li> <p><strong>[ Saghi]</strong> – Data Scientist<br/> He brings expertise in data analysis and machine learning, focusing on optimizing our models for accurate positioning.</p> </li> <li> <p><strong>[ Arzi]</strong> – Researcher &amp; Designer<br/> She ensures that our user interface is intuitive and user-friendly, enhancing the overall experience for end-users.</p> </li> </ul> <p>Together, our team is committed to advancing indoor positioning technology, making it more accessible and efficient for a variety of applications.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/IPS_3d-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/IPS_3d-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/IPS_3d-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/IPS_3d.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Positioning is Important </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Indoor Positioning System Team]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Javad finishes the Volume profile</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/Jaafari/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Javad finishes the Volume profile"/><published>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/Jaafari</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/Jaafari/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="kernel-density-estimation-kde">Kernel Density Estimation (KDE)</h2> <p>To overcome the discontinuities in the Volume Profile and to provide a more continuous estimate of price levels with significant trading volume, Kernel Density Estimation (KDE) can be employed. KDE is a non-parametric method for estimating the probability density function of a random variable and is defined as:</p> \[f_v(p) = \frac{1}{n} \sum_{i=1}^{n} K_h \left( \frac{p - p_i}{h} \right)\] <p>Where $p_i$ is the price on day $i$, $K_h(.)$ is the kernel function, and $h$ is the bandwidth of the kernel. The choice of kernel function and bandwidth affects the smoothness and accuracy of the resulting density estimate. A well-chosen bandwidth strikes a balance between too much noise (under-smoothing) and the loss of important details (over-smoothing).</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="toc"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volume profile]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Naji graduate in Indoor Positioning System</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/Naji/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Naji graduate in Indoor Positioning System"/><published>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-09-25T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/Naji</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/Naji/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="indoor-positioning-using-wi-fi-fingerprinting">Indoor Positioning Using Wi-Fi Fingerprinting</h2> <p>Author: Mohammad Amin Naji Meidani</p> <p>Supervisor: Prof. Hadi Sadoghi Yazdi</p> <p>Email: mohammadamin.najimeidani@mail.um.ac.ir</p> <h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2> <h3 id="applications-of-indoor-positioning">Applications of Indoor Positioning</h3> <p>Today, most outdoor positioning systems rely on satellites and are based on the <strong>Global Positioning System (GPS)</strong>. These systems are highly accurate for outdoor navigation but struggle with precise indoor positioning due to <strong>weakened satellite signals inside buildings</strong>. To address this issue, new technologies known as <em>indoor positioning systems</em> (IPS) have been developed. IPS is widely used in places like schools, offices, supermarkets, hospitals, and universities. For example, in supermarkets, shoppers can use a shopping cart with a digital guide screen and RFID tags to locate products. In museums, visitors can use Bluetooth and Wi-Fi devices to find information about exhibits. IPS can also assist students in finding specific shelves in a library and is used in targeted marketing, where advertisements are tailored to individuals’ preferences and locations within a building, such as sending clothing ads to those frequently visiting clothing stores.</p> <h3 id="problem-statement-and-research-motivation">Problem Statement and Research Motivation</h3> <p>One of the main challenges faced by visitors to large buildings such as offices, hospitals, stores, and universities is confusion and difficulty in <strong>finding the optimal route to their desired location.</strong> This issue leads to significant time and energy waste for both visitors and staff. Hence, there is a need for a system to guide visitors to their destinations. The focus of this research is to develop a <strong>ubiquitous and non-specialized indoor positioning system</strong>. The system should utilize <strong>existing infrastructure</strong> without requiring additional infrastructure or high costs for implementation. The aim is to create a prototype of an indoor positioning system based on mobile phones. The <strong>Faculty of Engineering at Ferdowsi University of Mashhad</strong> has been selected as the <strong>test environment</strong>, where the system will leverage the faculty’s <strong>Wi-Fi access points</strong> for positioning.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/imagesNaji/ips_applications-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/imagesNaji/ips_applications-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/imagesNaji/ips_applications-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/imagesNaji/ips_applications.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> Indoor Positioning Applications </div> <h3 id="system-overview">System Overview</h3> <p>The contributions of this thesis are divided into <strong>two sections</strong>: <strong>software related</strong> and <strong>machine learning</strong>. In the software section, the map of the Faculty of Engineering was first converted from the proprietary AutoCAD format to the <strong>GeoJSON format</strong>, which is an open-source format that can be used in applications. Then, an <strong>Android app</strong> was developed using the Flutter platform, responsible for recording Wi-Fi signals and displaying the predicted location on the map. The collected data is stored in a database on the <strong>server side</strong>, and the machine learning operations are also performed on the server. In the machine learning section, the <strong><em>fingerprinting method</em></strong> was used for positioning. In the offline phase, the data is cleaned and preprocessed, then stored in the database. To examine the effect of the number of reference points on positioning accuracy, <strong><em>Gaussian process regression</em></strong> was employed to enrich the offline phase data. In the online phase, a <strong>buffering mechanism</strong> was introduced to achieve less noisy and more reliable responses. The <strong><em>weighted k-nearest neighbors (k-NN) algorithm</em></strong> was used to predict the final location. Additionally, the impact of different <strong>distance metrics</strong> on prediction accuracy was investigated.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defence Note]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ali Forouzan near the end</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/AliForouzan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ali Forouzan near the end"/><published>2024-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-09-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/AliForouzan</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/AliForouzan/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="predicting-stock-price-breakouts-and-reversals-using-elastic-matching-and-probability-density-analysis">Predicting Stock Price Breakouts and Reversals Using Elastic Matching and Probability Density Analysis</h2> <p>By Ali Forouzan, Hadi Sadoghi Yazdi</p> <p><strong>Probability date for submission: October 10, 2024.</strong></p> <h2 id="part-of-abstract">Part of Abstract</h2> <p>Predicting stock price breakouts or reversals at critical chart levels—known as Change of Character (CHoCH)—is a complex challenge due to the intricate interplay between market data, global news, social media, and economic indicators. This paper introduces a novel methodology that leverages a vast network of interconnected information sources, advanced data analysis techniques, and sentiment analysis to forecast these pivotal market movements with unprecedented accuracy.</p> <div class="row mt-3"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" srcset="/assets/img/Blog/Breakout-480.webp 480w,/assets/img/Blog/Breakout-800.webp 800w,/assets/img/Blog/Breakout-1400.webp 1400w," sizes="95vw" type="image/webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/Blog/Breakout.jpg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1" width="100%" height="auto" loading="eager" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <div class="caption"> A breakout in the stock market refers to the point at which the price of a stock moves beyond a defined support or resistance level, often signaling the start of a new trend and attracting increased trading volume. </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="formatting"/><category term="images"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights ongoing efforts, developments]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Google Gemini updates: Flash 1.5, Gemma 2 and Project Astra</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Google Gemini updates: Flash 1.5, Gemma 2 and Project Astra"/><published>2024-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2024/google-gemini-updates-flash-15-gemma-2-and-project-astra/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing updates across our Gemini family of models and a glimpse of Project Astra, our vision for the future of AI assistants.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog</title><link href="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Displaying External Posts on Your al-folio Blog"/><published>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</published><updated>2022-04-23T23:20:09+00:00</updated><id>https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://h-sadoghi.github.io//blog/2022/displaying-external-posts-on-your-al-folio-blog/"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name></name></author></entry></feed>